titravel.hr 2019-06-30

# Privacy Policy

* * *

Privacy Policy

To Islands Travel d.o.o., tourist agency, Ruđera Boškovića 7, 21000 Split, Croatia, (below: Agency) respects the privacy and rights of the users of its website. Our obligations, defined by regulations about personal data protection, are dealt with very seriously and by this statement we confirm that.

With this statement, we wish to explain to all our users the way we handle the personal data we collect. Here you may also find out more about how to contact us in case you have questions regarding your personal data.

The data that are collected:

1\. By visiting our website, we use cookies inside your web browser. Every user can prohibit receiving cookies by editing/changing settings in their web browser. Cookies are used for faster browsing the agency pages, does not contain personal information and is important for identifying user preferences and for Google analytics (Google site for analyzing a particular site).

2\. Sending inquiries or bookings via contact form on the agency sites. The personal data collected during the booking process are name and surname, address, country, phone number and e-mail address.  
These information are used in order for the service via our site to be delivered in the best possible way. This data is shared only with the owner of the property you have booked. No promotional or marketing notifications come to your e-mail address, unless you had explicitly requested so during the registration process.

3\. Payments by credit cards

If you choose to pay for one of our services by credit card on our website, you will be asked to provide your credit card information. This information is entered on the security link that we send to you.  
The card is charged on the site and server of the online payment service provider. The Agency does not see or keep the data needed to charge the card.

4\. Getting notifications and newsletters

If you have marked, during the booking process, that you want to receive notifications and newsletters from our agency, you will receive them on your e-mail address. You can unsubscribe from that list at any time.

5\. Security and deleting the data

The collected data is stored on secure servers and only employees of the agency have access to it. For any other information you can contact b2b@titravel.hr
